Hi everyone, in this video I'm going to show you how to navigate the new site
using the
phone. So I've logged into my profile. This is the home page, so here you can
see all
of the members that are online. So when you log yourself on, you can always
check here
that you're online. Obviously there's many pages you can go through. So this is
webcam
and direct chat. Okay, so here I'm going to click on the menu and this is where
you can
go through all of these things to navigate the site. Up here is the emails and
bookings.
I'm not going to click into my emails just to keep my clients in privacy. So
yeah, in
there you'll respond to all of your emails from your clients. We recommend
doing this
as it's a good way to keep in touch with regular clients in between calls and
also just a really
good way to just let your clients know that you're online, to come and chat
with you.
So it is always a way of getting back to your emails. Of course you don't want
to be email
and someone too much if they've never come to a paid chat, but we do recommend
just getting
back to them as and when. Okay, so now we can start a look at the rest of the
features
on the site. Here you can click on my availability and this is where you can
broadcast now. There
are also other ways that you can go to broadcast. So here in setup webcam, but
we'll actually
come back to that. Okay, so also on the menu here you can see you can upload
your content.
So we recommend uploads and photos and videos to your profile as you can even
upload to
a private gallery and make money while you're not even on there. So yeah,
people compare
to your private gallery at any time. So it's always worth having one of those.
And again
here is where you can upload your movies. If you are interested in phone chat,
this is
where you click to enter all of your details for that. Bear in mind, they will
never get
your real phone number. It's always a diverted number. So this is good to use
as well. Also
another great way to keep in touch with your regular clients and make money of
course.
Okay, so now we will take a look at the direct cam settings. So if you want to
click here
on setup webcam. Okay, so here on special offers, you can make special offers
for your
clients. That's all done in this part here. Let's go back into setup webcam.
Okay, so
this one's quite important, your direct cam settings. One moment. Okay, didn't
load the
first time, but as you can see, if there's ever any issues, just click out of
it and click
back in and you'll get taken back to where you want. Okay, so I'll talk through
this
a little bit. So here, direct IM. This can either be enabled or disabled
whenever you'd
like to use it. Direct IM is basically the same as webcam, but without the
webcam. So
you're basically just chatting to them on a live back and forth and where they
can't
see you, it's just messages. So if you do turn on your direct IM, then down
here with
the group and private mode, you will have to change your settings and make it a
little
bit cheaper as they obviously don't pay as much for direct IM because they can
't see
you. So if I was to turn my direct IM on, I would probably put my rate to maybe
one credit
to pay a minute in group and 1.7 credits in private, let's say. If I was to
press save
now, that would put me on direct IM and then I'd be able to broadcast using
that. So let's
switch that back off for now and put the rate back. I forget what it was now,
but I'll just
do this for now. Okay, next we'll talk about free mode. So this is for when you
're on
webcam. So if you would like to use free mode, you can click here to enable
free mode and
then you get the option to let them in for a certain amount of time. You can do
5 minutes,
10 minutes, you can do up to unlimited. I personally wouldn't let them in your
free
chat for an unlimited amount of time as you don't want them in there for too
long. You
want them in there for a couple of minutes and then for them to take you to a
paid chat
and then here you can set within what time period. So mine is currently, they
can come
into my chat room for free for 5 minutes within every hour. So they can come in
for
5 minutes. It'll kick them out after 5 minutes and then after the next hour
they can then
come in for another 5 minutes. There's this box here that you could potentially
tick,
which says enable free guests, free preview to guests. I wouldn't tick this one
because
this is people who don't even have an account on the site. So it's less likely
that they've
got, you know, any intention of coming with you. Maybe they're just a free
loader. So
I wouldn't never normally tick this one. I only ever tick this one when I'm
doing free
mode as this means that people who've already got an account and potentially
got credits
in their account are ready to come with you. Okay, so what else can we look at
for the
settings? That's actually all for now and there so I'll just cancel. So none of
my,
none of my settings were changed. And down here there's a few more things you
can look
at for your webcam settings. For example, the category and strap line. So you
can click
on that and you can set yourself in a category mine. I'm currently in doms as I
like to dom
on there, but sometimes I put myself into my age category category. For example
, I put
myself in tasty 20s if I was going to do an age category, but sometimes I just
put myself
on doms. There's many in there. You can see what stands out to you most or what
suit you
most I should say. And here you can write your strap line. So this pops up when
they hover
over your profile. As you can see, I've got mine saying I'm feeling naughty
today, he-he.
But you can write whatever you want. And finally down here, if you want to
connect
your Twitter, that's where you will do it. Okay, let's take a look what else we
have on
the site. So again, going back, click back on to menu. And now we want to take
a look
at our credits. I'm going to have to cut this out because I don't actually know
where it
is. I don't even use this one. Where the hell is it? I never use this this way.
I always
use the desktop feature obviously. I had the button. Okay, let me just try my
text. So
it's just a bit of ability. Special office, I've got a preview of this. Okay,
so it's
just the credits and live on camera. Okay, now I'll show you how to look at
your credits.
So down here, you can click on credits. And then as you can see, it says I have
0.3 credits.
To be honest, this-this be here, you don't want to look at because this could
tell you
have an estate amount of credits that you've already been paid for. Basically,
these get
transferred out of your account every week or so. Yeah, we pay them to you
every day.
So don't look at this bit. If you ever want to check your credit statement, you
click
into here on credit statement. And this is where you can view your full credit
statement
and go through all of the different pages, see how much you've earned. We have
a full
video on this explaining how exactly to look at your credit statement and work
out what
you've made. So if you want to look at that in more detail, please visit our
credit statement
video. Okay, finally, I will show you how to go live on cam. So you're going to
click
up here in menu. You can click on setup webcam and then broadcast now. If
anything pops
up, you want to click allow to allow your camera and microphone to be used. And
here
we are. Okay, so up here in the top, you can see start. You want to click start
. You always
have to verify that you're the only person in your webcam. You cannot have any
people,
animals or photos in the background, just you in your camera. Okay, so now it's
going
to start to connect me to can. As you can see here, my microphone is on. So you
can click
this button here to turn it off or keep it on whatever you prefer. You can talk
or type
whatever is best for you. In here is where you'll type out your messages and em
ojis
can be seen here. If you click on this here, it shows you you'll have a list of
all the
clients that have came into your chat room, how long they've stayed, how much
they've
spent and whatnot. And then here also shows you the information. I'm going to
show you
as well up here is the boost button. Now this is very important. I personally
boost every
single time I go online. If I don't use free chat, I will boost. So the boost
button puts
you onto the front page of the website and free chat can also do this. But the
boost button
is guaranteed. So if you click on boost, it will always come up with a sitting
amount
of credits, but I always go back, I take it out until it goes to orange. And
then you'll
know, okay, that's not enough to get me onto the front page. But for credits
would be enough
as it's when green. But what I always do is I always actually put in an extra
credit because
that way it kind of guarantees you to be at the top of the front page. So I
didn't mind
paying that extra extra credit to do so. And then I'll just click on bid to
boost. And
then I will be on the front page for the next hour. As you can see here, the
next hour starts
in 11 minutes, 35 seconds. I would always do it at around 5 to 3 minutes to the
hour.
So if I was doing this in real time, I wouldn't be doing it now. I would wait a
little bit
longer. And you actually do get prompted in your chat room. So when you're
online, a message
will come up here just like this one. And it will say you can boost now or
something
like that. I don't know the exact words, but it tells you you're ready to boost
for
the next hour. And finally, here you can click on the settings and you can
actually do a
lot here as well. So a lot when I was showing you earlier on the main page can
also be accessed
from here. And I think it's a lot easier to access from here actually. So as
you can see,
I can tear my free mode on and off. I can change my prices. I can take a look
at what
microphone I'm using, what cameras being used, the quality, you know, the chat
size.
You can change the font, the sounds and some more settings there. So it's quite
easy that
you can do quite a lot from this page. But yeah, that is all for now. I hope
that this
was beneficial and helped you guys. If you ever need any more help or guidance,
please
let us know. And yeah, that's all for now. Good luck when you're next online. M
wah.